"风骚律师" 前情提要...
Previously on "Better Call Saul"...
四是解锁  五是上锁
Four for unlock, five for lock.
不得不说 这不像
I gotta tell ya, it does not sound like
我所知道的那个霍华德·哈姆林
the Howard Hamlin that I know.
忘记你们曾经听到过的霍华德·哈姆林的所有事
You're going to forget you ever heard the name Howard Hamlin.
拉罗死了
Lalo is dead.
地检办公室查出
The DA's office put it together
拉罗谎称自己叫德古兹曼
that Lalo was calling himself "de Guzman."
你觉得我们该怎么办
What do you think we should do?
你是愿意当贩毒集团的朋友
Do you want to be a friend of the cartel
还是当告密的叛徒
or do you want to be a rat?
-你有什么发现  -拉罗·塞拉曼加还活着
-What did you learn? -Lalo Salamanca lives.
不是吧
Oh, no.
认真的吗
Really?
我以为只是边框涂那个颜色
I thought it'd be just the trim.
有那么多颜色 干吗偏偏挑那个
Of all the colors, why would you pick that?
即便想选红色 也选奥多比红啊
Use adobe red, if you want red.
那算什么红色
What do you even call that?
消防车红
Fire engine red?
番茄红
Tomato red.
他们的邻居太可怜了
Their poor neighbors.
真是碍眼
What an eyesore.
业主协会绝对不会批准那个颜色
There's no way the Homeowners' Association approved that color.
巴布一定会气得火冒三丈
Barb's gonna have a cow.
或许我可以给她吹吹风
Maybe I could put a bug in her ear...
巴布能怎样
What can Barb do?
那里根本不是山景城的地界
That place isn't even in Mountain View.
归因前特蒙特山管辖
It's Enchantment Hills over there.
因前特蒙特山从皮农路开始
Enchantment Hills starts at Pinon Lane.
还记得维斯科雷科一家 种了那片颤杨吗
Remember when the Westlakes planted those Quaking Aspens?
那片破杨树
That whole mess?
维斯科雷科一家不是证明了 他们家的地属于因前特蒙特山吗
I thought the Westlakes proved their lot was in Enchantment Hills.
他们花钱做了土地调查
They paid for a land survey.
认真的吗
Really?
你从哪听说的
Where'd you hear that?
大概是罗比·戴维斯
Robbie Davis, maybe.
我冲完澡后再去地图上确认一下
I'll double-check the map after I shower.
你要喝吗
Want some?
不了
Nah. I'm good.
那是冰茶吗
Is that iced tea?
要不要喝点
Mrs. Would you like some?
没问题 谢谢 女士
Love some. Thank you, Ma'am.
最近怎么样
How's it going?
现状
Eh. Status quo.
一切都好
You know, hummin' along.
我们上周确实签下了一个大客户
We did land a pretty big client last week, though.
圣菲的一个保险装备公司
Insurance outfit in Santa Fe.
他们的客户基本上都是高端地产公司
They cover most of the high-end real estate up there.
好极了
Great.
但豪沃德 我不是股东
But, Howard, I'm not a shareholder.
我只是热热身
I'm -- I'm just getting warmed up.
尽管我还是觉得 你可以当个优秀的诉讼律师
Although I still think you would make one hell of litigator.
谢谢你的好意 但算了
Ah. Appreciate that, but I'll pass.
家里情况也差不多
At home, things are more or less the same.
没有变得更糟
It's not any worse --
我应该心存感激
I guess I should be grateful for that.
感觉我们…
It's like we're...
进入了死胡同
deadlocked.
雪柔还是习惯有什么事就憋在心里
Cheryl still won't talk about anything...important.
-你试过我们商量的办法吗  -试过
You tried what we discussed? Yes.
对 我试了 可是…
Yes, Idid, but...
我确实做了一个梦
I didhave a dream.
我就仔细看了我爸的票 明显那是一趟国际航班
So I look over the old man's ticket, and it's clearly an international flight,
所以我们就查他的登机口
so we search for his gate number --
但所有标志牌上 都是我看不懂的语言
but all the signs are in a language I can't read.
金
Kim!
路上车多吗
Any traffic?
没有 25号公路一路畅行
Nope. Straight shot down 25.
我们坐这桌
This is us.
谢谢你来见我
Thanks for meeting me.
我想着你来这里肯定忙得很
I imagine you're swamped when you're in town.
今天还好
Today's not too bad.
其实 我在你的老东家 施韦卡特还有个会
In fact, I have a meeting at your old stomping ground, with Schweikart.
那替我向里奇问好
Tell Rich I said hi.
没问题
Of course.
吉米怎么样
How's Jimmy?
他很好 谢谢关心
He's great. Thanks for asking.
爱丽丝怎么样
How about Alice?
她也很好
She's doing well.
她开始学烘焙 我的胃很是满足
She's taking up baking, and, uh, no complaints here.
-那你真幸运 -可不是嘛
Well, lucky you.Don't I know it.
我听说这里的拿铁一流
I hear this place makes a killer latte.
对 要我说的话 爪哇乔的对手出现了
Yeah. They give Java Joe's a run for their money, if you ask me.
（汽车旅馆办公室）
嘿
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
快来
Come on!
我刚接待完客户
Had a customer.
好 但我们该走了
Okay, okay, but it's time to go.
快 我们得赶紧出发
C'mon! We gotta get moving!
你要做什么
Wait. What are ya doing?
不行
No, no, no, no, no.
快点 我们得走了
Hey. Come on. We gotta move. We gotta move.
我买瓶根汁汽水
I'm getting a root beer.
不行 我们有安排 还记得吗  我们商量过的
No, no. We have a schedule. Remember? We discussed it.
可我投了五美分进去
I put two quarters in.
事成之后 我会给你买一整箱
I will buy you an entire case when we're done.
走吧 快上车
Here we go. Right in. Whew.
好好坐进去
All the way.
（准备好了）
没事吧
Everything okay?
没事
Sure.
用我再交待一次吗
Do we need to go over it again?
不用
Nah.
记住了 一定别站在碍事的地方
Well, just remember --keep your feet out of the way
因为我得一溜烟开走
'cause I'm gonna have to leave in a hurry.
怎么了
What?
我真的很喜欢你的头发
I really like your hair.
这不…
It's not --
谢谢
Thank you.
Thanks.
如果有别的办法呢
What if there was a different way?
如果设立一个独立的律师团队 或许四到五人
What if there was an independent team of lawyers -- maybe four or five of them --
专门接疑难杂案
who were dedicated to taking on the difficult cases?
我不是说几个律师 就能解决庞大的体制性问题
I'm not saying a few lawyers can solve a massive, systemic problem,
但他们可以改善情况
but they could make it better.
为什么找我呢
And why come to me with this?
如果我想糊弄你
Well, if I wanted to shine you on,
就会说那是因为人人都知道 你有很深的社会良知
I'd tell you it's because you're known for your social conscience.
但真正的原因是你在州政府有关系
But the truth is it's because of your connections in state government.
-你有能力施加影响 -没错
You can make things happen. Fair enough.
金 律师有一个服务委员会
Kim, the firm has a service committee.
我应该让你去找他们 跟其他有价值的案子保持一致
I should tell you to go to them and get in line with all the other worthy causes.
但这是动真格的 不是随口说说
But you're putting your money where your mouth is.
你肯定听说了我儿子吸毒的事
I'm sure you've heard something about my son's drug problem.
格里高利的挣扎
Gregory's struggle gave me a more,
这么说吧 让我对法律体制有了意见
let's say, personal view of the legal system.
金 我觉得这点子是可以的
Kim, I think you've got something here.
（开始）
但你不能略掉支持人员 他们是这一切的核心
You can't skimp on the support staff. They're the beating heart of the operation.
我们律所就是这样…
I know that's true in our office --
不要
No, no! No! No!
天啊…
Jesus.
你这混蛋
You son of a bitch!
你这心理扭曲 欠钱不还的人渣
You twisted deadbeat piece of shit!
那不是豪沃德吗
Wasn't that...Howard?
可恶 你欠我钱
God damn it! You owe me!
女士 你没事吧
Ma'am, are you okay?
-你欠我的  -女士
You owe me! Ma'am...
-可是… -还没人敢这么对我
I mean...Nobody does that to me!
我说不好 一切太快了
I don't know. It happened so fast.
该死 你欠我的 这是欺诈
Damn it! He owes me! What a rip-off!
可恶
Damn you!
不是吧
No. No!
他们把路锥拿走了
They moved the cone?!
什么混蛋会拿走路锥
What kinda asshole moves a cone?!
该死
Ohh. Crap.
（病人专用停车位）
（岔路口汽车旅馆）
嘿 听着
Hey, listen. Um...
一定要当心 知道吗
Be careful, okay?
知道了
Okay.
-怎么了  -执法部门
What? Five-O.
这下我今天生意没得做了
That kills business for the rest of the day.
他们总是烦我
Always hassling me.
-卧底警察  -对
Undercover cops? Yep.
听着 如果你惹上法律麻烦 就给我打电话
Well, listen, if you ever have any legal problems, give me a call,
随时都行 不收费
anytime. No charge.
谢谢
Thanks.
所以我把捷豹车停在卸货区
So I pulled the Jag into the loading zone
然后开始拽那块大金属牌
and I start scrapping with this hunk of metal.
老天
Oh, my God.
那牌子插得好深 感觉深不见底
It was in deep. Like down-a-well deep.
所以我就像一头愤怒的小熊 跟它搏斗 然后…
So I just...wrestled it! Nngh! Like a freakin' bear! And I -- nngh!
一口气把它栽进了 捷豹车前面的土里 砰
-- jam it in the dirt in front of the Jag. Boom!
差那么一点点就跟豪沃德撞上了
Barely made it out of there by the skin of my teeth.
谁会动别人的路锥 谁会做这种事
Who moves cones?! Who does that?
自恋狂
Narcissists.
你说得太对了
You're damn right.
-你觉得克里夫真的信了吗  -绝对信了
So you think Cliff really bought it, huh? One hundred percent.
你该看看他的表情
You should have seen his face.
我们成功了 相信我
It landed, trust me.
老天 简直太妙了
God, it was beautiful.
-还不止这件事呢 -说说看
Oh. And that is not all. Spill.
我为了拖延时间 就告诉克里夫 自己在做什么 以及之后的计划
So, I'm doing the stall, I'm telling Cliff what I'm doing, what I wanna be doing.
我脑子里想的全是 得尽力发挥 直到你过来
All I'm thinking about is I gotta stretch this out until you get there.
但后来 我说不好 我就有点上头了
But then, I don't know, I kind of got caught up in it.
然后…
And then...
克里夫就被说动了
Cliff went for it.
完全被说动了
I mean, like, really went for it.
什么意思 他要出钱吗
What does that mean? Like money?
他应该不会自己出钱
I-I don't think he'll write a check himself.
但他有人脉 一定会帮上忙
But he knows people. And I think he'll deliver.
你在开玩笑吧
You're kidding.
-我知道 是不是很棒  -真是不可思议
I know! How great is that? This is unbelievable.
我们就是连连开门红
Are we on a roll or are we on a roll?
哎呀
Geez.
你有没有感觉自己被跟踪了
You ever feel like you're being followed?
我把温迪送回汽车旅馆时
When I dropped Wendy off at the motel,
她觉得自己被几个卧底警察盯上了
she thought she was being watched by some undercover cops.
但后来我开走时 那辆车又跟着我
But then, when I drove away, that same car was behind me.
被我发现后 他们就不见了
Right after I spotted them, they disappeared.
常言道“恶人虽无人追赶也逃跑”
Well, you know what they say. "The wicked flee when no man pursueth."
你觉得我们是恶人
You think we're wicked?
不是 怎么了 就是一个说法
No. What? It's just a turn of phrase.
我觉得你倒是“婀”娜多姿
I think you're wicked hawt.
好了
Alright.
听听我这个过来人的看法 知道你怎会怎么想吗
Listen to the voice of experience, okay? You know why you're feeling like this?
因为我们脱身了
Because we got away with it.
事情顺利到让人觉得不是真的
It seems too good to be true.
但相信我 没人在跟踪你
But trust me, nobody is following you.
除了我们之外 没人知道这些事 好吗
No one knows what we're doing except for us. Okay?
知道了
Okay.
我懂 在这种情况下 我跟你一样
I get it. Under the circumstances, I wouldn't want to be
也想尽量远离警局
anywhere near a police station if I were you either.
听着 我要修理议室的红木桌子
I'll tell you what. Um, the mahogany in my conference room is currently getting buffed out,
所以在用胡安塔布路 和天际线路交口的附属办公室
so I'm using my satellite office at Juan Tabo and Skyline.
我把大厅让给了美甲店 所以我办公室在后面
I'm letting a nail salon, you know, use the lobby, so my office is in the back.
你3点过去找我
Meet me there at00.
好极了 谢谢 你怎么样 大史
Great! Thanks. How's it hanging, Steve-O?
-鞋子 皮带和外套 都脱掉 -抱歉 什么
Shoes. Belt. Jacket. I'm sorry. What?
鞋子 皮带和外套
Shoes. Belt. Jacket.
你认真的吗
Seriously?
什么时候开始的
Since when?
-这是流程 先生 -“先生”
It's procedure, sir. "Sir"?
（超级扫描仪）
-怎么就我中大奖了  -谁说得准啊
Why'd Ihit the jackpot? Never can tell.
嘿 今天天气不错 你还好吗
Hey. How you doing on this beautiful day?
卡洛斯生日那天 你看到我送的饼干花束没
Did you, uh, catch that cookie bouquet that I sent for Carlos' birthday?
我还专门为了你 额外放了一些白巧克力夏威夷果
'Cause I put a few extra white chocolate macadamias in there, just for you.
你有什么事
What do you need?
我吗 没什么事
Me? Uh - Nothing. Nothing!
但我一个“朋友” 希望将预审听证会改期
But I have a "friend" who could use a --a preliminary hearing rescheduled.
冈萨雷斯诉新墨西哥州政府案
Uh, Gonzalez v. New Mexico.
我“朋友”希望改到 周五上午大概9点
My "friend" is looking for a Friday around nine a.m. --
在法官喝第四杯咖啡之前
you know, before the judge's fourth cup of coffee
因为咖啡因诱发的不安 会让辩护律师很吃亏
because, uh, caffeine jitters --they're brutal on the defense, so...
什么朋友
What "friend"?
你们应该没有见过
I don't believe you two have met.
-这是什么  -听证会改期申请表
What is this? A hearing change request form.
嘿 拜托 是我啊
Hey, come on. It's me...
看啊 妈妈 我刚毕业了
Look, Mommy. I just graduated.
我不会用笔
I -- I can't use a pen.
我没有对生拇指
I have no opposable thumbs.
（关闭）
嘿 小汉娜
Hey! Hannah Banana!
嘿 你好
Hey, yourself.
拜托 比尔 怎么能这样对待女士
Come on, Bill. That's no way to treat a lady.
你得讨人家的欢心 比尔 要温柔点 这样才对
You got to make love to it, Bill. You know, be gentle -- that's the way to do it.
想着巴里·怀特 想着诱惑
Think Barry White, think seduction.
到底怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
大家怎么看见我就像见了瘟神一样
How come everyone's treating me like I'm covered in oozing pus sores?
我还是更喜欢你只是耍小聪明的时候
I liked you better when you were just a regular bottom feeder.
-但这样… -“这样”
But this... "This"?
“这样”是哪样
What is "this"?
我理解你要为客户着想
I understand advocating for your client.
我真心理解
Deep in my heart, I get it.
但你欺骗法庭 欺骗法官
But you scammed the court, you scammed the judge.
为了什么呢
And for what?
把贩毒集团一个杀人魔头放回社会
To get a murdering cartel psychopath back out on the street?
这真的…
It's just...
很不对
wrong.
比尔 你不能信口开河 拿出证据来
That's a lotta big talk, Bill. Prove it.
拿出证据来 比尔
Prove it, Bill!
证明是一回事
There's proving,
知道是另一回事
and then there's knowing.
阿比…
Abe,
你不想回县监狱 对吧
you don't want to go back to county, do you?
好的 那就…
Okay. So
-去见面  -我会去
the meetings? I'll go.
好极了
Great.
那我们周二见 上午9点整
Then I'll see you Tuesday, nine a.m. sharp.
你想吃吗
You want this?
想
I do.
慢慢吃
Take your time.
好了 我就回来
好好享受
Enjoy.
你随便坐 没关系
Yeah, you can sit anywhere you want. That's fine.
阿比 能帮我看一下东西吗
Abe, would you mind watching my stuff?
（艾尔卡米诺餐厅）
-嘿 -你好
Hey. Hello.
天气不错
Nice day.
你们在跟踪我吗
Are you following me?
你说什么
I'm sorry?
你们在跟踪我吗
Are you following me?
你们是谁 阿尔伯克基警局
What are you, APD?
知道吗
Know what?
我觉得你们在跟踪我 如果你们不亮明身份
Ithink you're following me, and if you're not gonna identify yourselves,
那我就去查车牌号了 因为我感觉受到了威胁
then I'm calling in your plates because I feel threatened.
抱歉打扰你了
Sorry if we've disturbed you.
祝你今天愉快 女士
You have a nice day, ma'am.
索尔·古德曼 你的正义从不迟到
Saul Goodman, speedy justice for you.
不 第一次咨询免费
Uh, no, there's no charge for the initial consultation.
今天吗 好
Today? Yeah, um...
我3点半有空档
I have an opening around30.
我在附属办公室上班
Oh, I'm working out of my satellite office.
就在胡安塔布路和天际线路交口
It's at Juan Tabo and Skyline.
我把大厅让给了一个美甲店 所以办公室在后面
I'm letting a nail salon use the lobby, so office is in back.
没问题 你叫什么
Great. Uh, your name?
丹特
Dante.
那到时候见
See you then.
索尔·古德曼 你的正义从不迟到
Saul Goodman, speedy justice for you.
对 我…对 我今天确实有空档…
Yeah. Uh, yeah. I do have an opening today --
等一下 我有个电话
Oh, hold on. I'm getting another call.
索尔·古德曼 你的正义从不迟到
Saul Goodman, speedy justice for you.
请稍等一下
Um, hold, please.
抱歉
My apologies.
我今天业务有点繁忙
I'm having a bit of a rush here today.
（日间水疗及美甲）
马上让那些人出去
You get these people out right now.
-你说他们吗 他们打扰到你了吗  -不是他们 里面的人
What? These guys? Are they bothering you? Not them. Inside!
谁来见索尔·古德曼
Who's here to see Saul Goodman?
就是你吗 你是索尔
You're him? You're Saul?
是我
Yeah.
你就是那个人 对吧
Then you're the guy, right?
什么人
What guy's that?
萨拉曼卡的律师
Salamanca's guy.
是我
Yeah.
That's me.
已经约好的人…
Everybody who has an appointment already --
知道吗
Uh, oh, you know -- you know what?
一位叫斯普吉的先生…
Uh, Mr. "Spooge"?
叫我“斯普吉”就好
It's just "Spooge."
斯普吉就好 知道了 没问题
Just Spooge. Duly noted. Alright.
盖尔·莫伦戈
Um, Gael Morengo?
好的 我看看…
Okay. Uh, let's see.
有没有叫丹特的
Is there a Dante?
还有洛克·库伯勒
And Rocco Kubler. Okay.
好了 其他人麻烦请去外面等候
Everybody else, um, kindly wait outside,
好吗
alright?
除非你们想边等边享受水疗服务
Unless -- Unless you desire spa services while you wait.
这要另外收费 但我强烈建议大家体验一下
Uh, that's a separate charge, but it-- it's highly recommended.
这里是阿尔伯克基最好的美甲店
The -- The best pedicures in Albuquerque, right here.
六号…
Six.
幸运号码七…你跟他一起的吗
Lucky number seven. Oh, you're with him?
八号…
And eight.
皮衣不错
Nice leathers.
好 你们一起的
Uh, okay, together.
然后是…九号
And nine.
感谢各位的耐心
Um, thank you all for your patience.
还有…
And...
为所有人讨回公道
justice for all!
付钱的顾客才能喝黄瓜水
Cucumber water for paying customers only.
相信我 他们会付钱
Oh, believe me, they're gonna be paying.
斯普吉
"Spooge"!
斯普吉和朋友 好的
Oh, Spooge and friend. Okay.
好 这边请
Good. This way.
嗨 女士
Hi, ma'am.
很好 洗衣机那里左拐
Yeah, hang -- hang a left at the washing machine.
没错
There you go.
我们下周见 罗莎 很高兴见到你 皮拉尔
I'll see you next week, Rosa. And it was nice meeting you, Pilar.
别忘了尽量带更多家人来
Don't forget to bring as many family members as you can.
-我们会的 谢谢 韦克斯勒女士 -保重
We will. Thank you, Ms. Wexler. Take care.
-今天忙完了吗  -对 给你
All done for today? Yeah. Here you go.
不用找了 谢尔比
Just keep it, Shelby.
-谢谢 金 我们明天见  -肯定的
Thanks, Kim. See you tomorrow? You bet.
他们走了
They're gone.
你说什么
I'm sorry?
那两个跟踪你的男人
The two men that were following you.
他们走了
They're gone.
我们认识吗
Do I know you?
坐下聊聊吧
Would you mind sitting for a moment?
我会回答能回答的问题
And I will answer any questions I can.
我派了人监视你和你丈夫
I have men watching you and your husband.
我不是警察 据我所知
I'm not with the police, and as far as I know,
他们没在调查你俩
they're not investigating either of you.
不过我确实知道你们做了一些
I doknow that you've been up to a few things
不太想让别人知道的事
that you probably would rather keep private.
我不在乎
I don't care.
这不是我的目的
That's not what this is about.
我是想解决自己的一个问题
I'm trying to solve a problem of my own.
什么问题
What problem?
拉罗·萨拉曼卡
Lalo Salamanca.
拉罗·萨拉曼卡死了
Lalo Salamanca's dead.
他…
He...
没死吗
isn't.
我们在监视他可能会联系的人
We're watching anyone he might contact.
包括你和你丈夫
That includes you and your husband.
他不太可能联系你们 毕竟他在下一盘更大的棋
Most likely, he'll never reach out. He's got bigger fish to fry.
但要是有千分之一的几率 他联系你们了…
But in the thousand-to-one chance that he does...
你为谁做事
And who do you work for?
我说过只回答能回答的问题
I said I would answer anything I can.
你是沙漠里那个人
You're the guy from the desert.
跟吉米一起走出沙漠的人
The one who was out there with Jimmy.
你干吗跟我说 不去找他
Why are you telling methis and not him?
因为我觉得你更扛事
Because I think you're made of sterner stuff.
好了
Alright.
这样对大家都好
Now here's what's best for everyone.
如果你再看到我的人 希望你不会看到
You spot my guys again, which I'm hoping you won't,
让他们做自己的工作
let them go about their business.
假装他们不在那里
Just pretend they're not there.
很快他们就会消失
And pretty soon they won't be.
你和你丈夫 你们就…
You and your husband just...
好好过你们的日子
go on living your lives.
我认识你
I doknow you.
你之前在法院停车场工作
You worked in the parking booth at the courthouse.
你是那个管理员
You're the attendant.
曾经是
I was.
在美联储收紧利率之前
The markets will continue to be in a state of flux
市场将继续处于波动状态
until the Fed tightens interest rates.
有些时候 我们对经济复苏的速度感到满意
Some days we'll feel pretty good about the rate of economic recovery,
其他时候 就不怎么样了
other days not so much.
等一下 我好像在哪看到过
Mrs. I think I saw that somewhere.
-在哪  -这里
Here! Mrs.
不是
Nope.
你那个边缘拼得怎么样了
How's youredge coming along?
我还缺两块
I'm still missing two...
你那个边缘都找到了拼块
Mr. You found all your edge pieces.
应该是
I thought I did.
或许我们弄丢了几个
Maybe we lost a few.
这些树快把我弄死了 它们看起来完全一样
These trees are killing me. The pieces all look exactly the same.
有一辆绿色的福特面包车
Then work on the cabin.I could.
他跟了我差不多三个街区
There was a green Ford van. It was behind me for almost three blocks.
1998年款的伊克莱 我们查过车牌了
A '98 Econoline. We ran the plate.
那人是个自营管道工 他没问题
Guy's a freelance plumber. He's legit.
你安插在我厨房的那个人…
The man you placed in my kitchen.
罗伊
Roy.
你跟我说他是个有经验的快餐厨师
You told me that he had experience as a short-order cook.
他上大学时在麦当劳打过两年工
Two years at McDonald's in college.
他在那里不只是为了炸薯条 我需要你身边有人
He's not there just to make French fries. I need guys in close.
他不符合炸鸡兄弟的标准
He's not up to Pollos standards.
我会找人替他
I'll find a replacement.
我们现在人手不够
We're stretched thin.
我的人在散布在镇上各处 每天工作18个小时
I've got guys working 18-hour days all over town.
已经两周了 一点动静都没有
Two weeks. We haven't had a tickle.
所以呢
And?
恕我冒昧 其他人都觉得那家伙死了
All due respect, the rest of the world thinks the guy is dead.
拉罗·萨拉曼卡还活着
Lalo Salamanca is alive.
那他在哪
Then where is he?
嘿
Hey.
你今天怎么样
How was your day?
来这里做什么
Uh, what are we doing here?
好好看看 你觉得怎么样
Take a look. What do you think?
什么怎么样
About what?
我潜在的新办公室 走吧
My new office. Potentially. Come on.
阮太太把我扫地出门了
Mrs. Nguyen kicked me to the curb.
什么 为什么
What? Why?
说来话长
It's a long story,
简而言之 就是她怀着很大的偏见 把我赶了出来
but upshot is she wants me outta there with extreme prejudice.
（商业地产 出租)
那你今天很不顺吧
Bad day, huh?
不 我今天很顺利
No. It was a great day.
接待了真正会付钱的客户
With actual paying clients.
名气已经打出去了
The word is out!
人们为了雇索尔·古德曼当律师 不惜豪掷退休金
People are throwing cash retainers at me -- just to say Saul Goodman is their lawyer.
因为你代理过那个人
Because of who you represented.
这只是一部分的原因
Well, I mean, that's part of it.
但关键是我需要尽快找个新办公室
But, um, the bottom line is I need a new place to do business -- pronto.
这地方虽然像狗窝一样 但是租金不高
Now, this place is a shithole, but the price is right
我可以跟房东谈谈 按月租赁
and I think I can talk the landlord into a month-to-month.
所以只是暂时的 直到我找到更好的地方
So it's temporary, you know, 'til I find something better.
嘿
Hey.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
这里又小
It's small.
又脏
It's...dirty.
而且气味也怪怪的
And this whole place smells funny.
可法院就离这里五个街区远
But the courthouse is five blocks away.
在去往大都会拘留中心的必经之路上
You can't get to MDC without driving past.
停车也方便 保释中心也不远 还有…
Parking is good, bail bond row isn't far, and, uh...
牛脸肉塔可也很近
Taco Cabeza is just around the corner.
所以这地方可能是块璞玉
Might be a diamond in the rough.
但你要答应我…
Just promise me...
不要移马桶
...you won't move the toilet.
那就这样 好的
There it is. Alright.
说到牛脸肉塔可…
Um, speaking of the Taco Cabeza...
我要饿死了 我们去吃吧
I'm starving. Let's do it.
字幕翻译: 吴春燕